Pick a card.
選一張
All right. Now,memorize it.
好 記住花色號碼
-You got it? -Oh, yes.
好了沒？ 好了
Is that your card?
是這張嗎？
Yes.
就是這張
-Hey,guys. -Hi there!
大家好
Guess what. Ben is gonna be in a TV commercial.
你們猜怎麼著？ 班要上電視拍廣告了
What are you talking about?
你們在說什麼？
It's not for sure,but...
還沒有定案
...we met this guy in the park who thought Ben was cute.
不過我們在公園裡遇到一個人 他覺得班很可愛
You know,which he is. He gave us his card...
這也是事實啦 那個人留了張名片
...and told us to bring him for this commercial he's auditioning.
要我帶班去參加廣告試鏡
This guy's the biggest commercial casting director in town!
這個人是本地最大的選角導演
Ben takes one lousy walk in the park and gets an audition?
班去公園隨便散個步 就有試鏡自動送上門！
I mean, way to go, Ben!
我是說，班，真有你的
I've been in that park a million times and no one's offered me an audition.
那個公園我都去爛了 從來沒人主動找我去試鏡
It's crazy. We were pushing Ben on the swings
我知道，真的很神奇 我們只是在陪班玩蕩鞦韆…
I'm always on the swings!
我每次都在玩蕩鞦韆啊
What am I doing wrong?
我是哪裡做錯了？
That.
就是那裡
The One Where Rachel Smokes
本集播出：「打入抽煙圈」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-Gotta go. Wish me luck. -Good luck.
我要出門了，祝我好運
Since you work at Ralph Lauren, can you get me some shirts?
瑞秋，既然你在拉夫羅倫工作 能不能帶幾件馬球衫回來？
I don't know if I'd feel comfortable stealing on my very first day.
第一天上班就偷公司東西 我可能下不了手喔
Unwilling to steal from work.
不願意慷公司之慨
Interesting.
有意思了
If anybody gets free stuff, it's me.
就算有人能拿免費的 那也非我莫屬
Okay,guys,way to wish me luck.
好了，各位，祝我好運吧
Go get 'em!
祝你好運，給他們好看
Let's discuss Rachel's birthday.
好，來討論幫瑞秋慶生的事
I say we throw a surprise party this weekend.
我建議在週末辦驚喜派對
But her birthday's not for another month.
可是一個月後才是她生日啊
If we throw her party on her birthday, it's not a surprise.
是沒錯，但在生日當天開派對 那就不驚喜啦
Great! We can have a dinner party and just invite her close friends.
我覺得這主意不錯 我們辦個晚餐派對 邀請好朋友過來
Ross! We're having a surprise party for Rachel.
羅斯！ 我們要幫瑞秋辦驚喜派對咯
Done.
搞定
Great. Wanna do it together?
好，那你要一起來嗎？
I'd love to do it together!
樂意之至
They're gonna do it together.
她們要一起來耶
That's my girlfriend.
兄弟，那位可是我女友
So I gotta shut it down now?
所以我就得閉嘴？
I gotta go. I'm picking up Ben...
好，我得走了 我要接班...
...and then we're off to the big audition.
...去參加大試鏡
It's gonna be weird seeing some actor pretending to be Ben's dad.
看到有演員假裝是班的父親 那種感覺一定很怪
Weirder than seeing his two moms make out?
是啊 怪過看班的兩個媽媽溫存？
Dad? There's a dad in the commercial?
爸爸？廣告裡面有爸爸？
Yeah. The dad and Ben eat soup and pretend to enjoy it.
是啊，班和爸爸喝湯 演得很陶醉的樣子
Maybe I'll go with you and audition as the dad.
或許我可以跟你們一起去 搞不好能試鏡演那個爸爸
Who better to play Ben's father than his godfather?
說到扮演班的爸爸 由我這教父上場更最適合了
-You're not his godfather. -What?
你不是班的教父 什麼？
Are you kidding?
你在開玩笑吧？
Of course I am.
當然是啊
-Okay, let's go, godfather. -All right!
我們走吧，教父 好耶
They're gonna let me audition!
我獲選了，他們讓我試鏡
Really? That's great!
真的？太棒了
One of the casting ladies has actually seen me in a play.
有個女的看過我演舞台劇
So I steered clear of her.
所以我離她離得遠遠的
And the other one,I know from....
另一個我也認識
Well,you know.
原因你也知道…
-That kid looks familiar. -Oh,yeah.
那個孩子看起來很眼熟 是啊
He's done tons of commercials. I've seen him in Sugar Smacks, PlayStation...
他拍過一堆廣告 有糖果廣告、新力PS遊戲機
...and that one for the phone company.
還幫電話公司拍過廣告
He was so good,he convinced me to switch phone companies.
他演得實在是太好了 我索性跟著換了電話公司
Chandler was mad.
錢德因此還氣得半死
He's not gonna get this one. Ben is way cuter than that kid.
不過他這次休想拿到這角色 因為班比他可愛多了
I mean, look at him.
看就知道，寶貝，看看你
That's great.
很好
Wouldn't it be great if I got to play Ben's dad?
不過若我能演班的爸爸 這樣是不是很棒？
You look nothing like Ben.
喬伊，你跟班一點都不像
I look more like him than you do.
比你跟他像多了
I really don't know you well enough for you to do that.
我跟你還不熟 哪裡生得出小孩？
So it's down to these two. Nancy,I know you like this one.
現在是最後的二選一 南茜，我知道你喜歡這一個
I think I agree. Rachel,what do you think?
我也有同感 瑞秋，你覺得呢？
Well, that one is pretty...
那個是很漂亮
...but I just love this fabric.
但我超愛這個的質料
Sorry.
抱歉了
Don't be. Part of your job is to give your opinions.
不用抱歉 提供意見是你的職責之一
Then I take credit for them. I'm kidding!
功勞歸我，開玩笑的
She is kidding. But don't ever disagree with her again.
她這次是在開玩笑 但下次可別跟她意見相左
Okay,now I'm kidding!
這次換我在開玩笑
What a fun office.
這個辦公室真有趣
I don't know which one. But I do know I need a cigarette.
我不知道要選哪一個 不過先來根煙倒是真的
Let's take a break, go outside and sort this out when we return.
不如我們出去休息一下 等回來之後再解決？
-You smoke? -No.
你抽煙嗎？ 不抽
My dad's a doctor. And he would always tell me horror stories....
不抽，我爸是醫生 老跟我說些恐怖的故事…
About ghosts and goblins...
說那些鬼神精靈的…
...who totally supported the princess' right to smoke.
完全贊同公主抽煙
And then they came back from smoking and they'd made all of the decisions.
她們在抽煙的時候 就背著我做出了決定
-That's not fair. -I know.
這樣不太公平 我知道啊！
It's like I'm being punished for not having this disgusting, poisonous habit.
我不同流合污還被處罰！ 抽煙可是噁心又傷身的習慣
Yeah, it is the best.
對，抽煙最棒了
What if this keeps happening?
萬一這種事沒完沒了怎麼辦？
They'll be smoking, making the decisions...
她們在外頭抽煙做決定
...and I'll be up in my office breathing in my stupid clean air.
我只能在辦公室裡 呼吸愚蠢的新鮮空氣
And when Kim wants to promote one of us...
到時等阿金要升我們的職
...who do you think she'll pick? Me or Smokey Smokerson?
你們想她會選誰？ 是我還是烏煙瘴氣的冒煙女？
We used to have a smoking area at work.
我們以前的公司有抽煙區
It was great. There was this big flowerpot with dirt in it.
很棒的喔 有個小花盆，裡頭有土
We used to put our cigarettes out in it.
把煙放進去捻熄就行了
One of the old-timers told me there used to be a little tree in there.
公司有個元老告訴我 以前裡頭還有棵小樹呢
You can go down there and not smoke. Say you want some fresh air.
瑞秋，你也可以一起去 不用抽煙，就說要去透透氣
I could do that.
對，這是方法
Or you could do the easy thing and smoke.
簡單點的就是一起抽煙
You gotta take long, deep drags.
深深吸它個一口
Wow,I still don't have my lung capacity back yet.
我的肺活量還沒恢復
Rach, do you wanna go get coffee?
瑞秋，要去喝咖啡嗎？
-I would love to. -Oh,good.
樂意之至 好
I'm gonna go too.
寶貝，我也想一起去
Oh,good.
好啊
Oh,I changed my mind.
等等，我變卦了
Let's talk about the party. I have so many ideas.
好，來討論派對的事 我有一大堆點子
Me too!
我也是
Oh,look at that.
真是壯觀
This is a little sketch of the cake. See?
好，這是蛋糕的素描圖
Some sample menus.
還有一些菜單的樣本
I thought we'd start with a Tuscan-style finger food.
不如用異國小點心當前菜
And for music, here's an alphabetized list of all of my CDs.
至於音樂呢 這是我CD收藏的字母列表
I've highlighted the ones that'll go with the food.
跟食物超搭配的還做了記號
-What about the intimate dinner party? -We're not doing that.
不是說要親密的晚餐派對嗎？ 現在不那樣做了
Looks like you took care of everything. Thanks a lot,cohost.
看來你全包辦了，多謝 「共同」主辦人
Wait a minute. There's plenty of things for you to do.
怎麼了？我沒有一手包辦啊 你要做的事還有很多
Like what?
舉個例子？
Cups.
杯子
You're giving me cups?
杯子？你讓我準備杯子？
And ice.
還有冰塊
Cups and ice? I get to be in charge of cups and ice?
杯子和冰塊？ 我可以負責杯子和冰塊？
All right.
好吧…
Fine. I will be in charge of cups and ice.
行，我就來負責杯子和冰塊
-I can get ice at the restaurant -I got it!
等等，冰塊可以從餐廳拿… 冰塊是我的！…
-How did the audition go? -Not so good.
試鏡順利嗎？ 不太順利
Wait a minute. Are you doing Joey's:
慢著，你在學喬伊那招嗎？
"The audition didn't go so well.... Yeah,it did"?
「試鏡不太順利」 事實上很順利！對吧？
Yeah,I am!
沒錯！
-Yeah,Ben got a second audition. -That's great!
班取得了第二次試鏡的資格 太棒了
I had to teach Ross my bit because I actually didn't get a callback.
我得教導羅斯我的戲份 因為我沒有過關
You got a callback too, didn't you?
你也過關了，對吧？
Yeah,I did!
沒錯！
What are you doing out here?
瑞秋，你怎麼會來這裡？
It got kind of lonely up there, so I thought I would come out here...
裡頭有點無聊 我想說來這裡...
...and get some fresh air.
...透透氣
We're discussing the fall collection.
南茜和我正好討論到秋裝
Oh,great.
太好了
Anyway,we really
所以這是要…
-Sorry. We're smoking all over you. -That's okay.
抱歉，瞧你被我們熏的 不好意思 沒關係
We'll move. You stay there.
不成…你待著，我們走
I sent the designs to Ralph. He was excited about it.
反正我把設計寄給拉夫 他對襯裡很中意
That's great! You are the best!
太好了，你是最棒的
Excuse me. Can I bum one of those?
不好意思，能給支煙嗎？
Actually, this one's....
這支就好…
What's so funny over here?
你們在聊什麼好笑的？
I thought you didn't smoke.
我還以為你不抽煙的
You know,I thought you guys meant marijuana cigarettes.
我以為你們是說大麻煙
You know what I mean? Doobies?
像是天使塵那種
Actually,I thought to myself, "Those guys are crazy!"
我還納悶你們是瘋了不成
But no,I smoke the regular ones all the time.
沒啦，我自己也抽煙 照三餐天天都抽
We get high.
我們是在抽大麻
Me too.
我也是
I'm kidding.
鬧你的
Me too.
我也是
Oh,God! This is so nerve-racking. How do you do this?
老天，這真是折磨人 你是怎麼習慣的？
Fortunately,I don't get many callbacks, so....
我過關的經驗不多，所以…
Is it a good sign that they asked us to wait?
我們在試鏡之後被留下來 這是好現象嗎？
Who knows?
天知道
We have narrowed it down to Raymond, Ben, Kyle...
最後入圍的是雷蒙、班 凱爾...
...and Joey. The rest of you,thank you.
和喬伊 其餘的人，辛苦了，謝謝
Yes! I knew it!
好耶，我就知道！
Bye-bye.
再會
So long.
別過
Later.
後會有期
I'm not married to him anymore. He's my ex-husband. I'm totally gay!
我不是他老婆喔，他是我前夫 我百分之百是女同志
This is great! I might get to play Ben's dad.
太棒了 我有可能飾演班的爸爸
Actually,that can't happen.
其實那是不可能的
Because you have such different looks...
因為你們各自的長相都不同
...we're putting you with Raymond and Kyle with Ben.
所以我們把你和雷蒙配對 凱爾和班是一組
So it'll either be you two or you two.
所以最後只有一組會出線
-This is gonna be kind of weird. -Yeah,it is.
要命，這樣就有點尷尬了 真的是
Yeah. It's gonna be weird.
對，一定會很尷尬
No. We're like best friends. That's why it's weird.
因為我們是最好的朋友 所以才會尷尬
I thought we were just talking.
原來如此…我只是答腔而已
If Ben gets this commercial, do you think you can get me some free soup?
如果班拿到廣告演出機會 你能幫我弄些免費的湯嗎？
Chandler, a can of soup is like 60 cents.
錢德，一罐湯又不用多少錢
Yeah, okay,but I have been supporting a 29-year-old ltalian for five years.
對，但是我這五年來 都在供養這29歲的意大利人
Is it okay if I leave this here till Rachel's birthday party?
我能把這些東西放這裡 等著給瑞秋過生日嗎？
-Sure. What's in them? -Cups.
當然可以，裡頭是什麼？ 杯子
Good, because we got Rachel 800 gallons of water.
那好，因為我們替瑞秋 準備了八百加侖的水
That's a lot of cups.
老實說，這些杯子還真不少
I'm in charge of cups and ice.
對，這是因為我負責杯子和冰塊
And Monica's gonna rue the day she put me in charge of cups and ice.
摩妮卡在這一天將後悔莫及 因為她要我負責杯子和冰塊
You know,I rued the day once. Didn't get a whole lot else done.
我也後悔過一次 除了後悔沒做別的
Okay, time to bring up the rest of the cups.
好吧，該把其他杯子搬上來了
喬伊 菲比
Ross, I'm glad you're here.
羅斯，你在這裡正好
-I want to talk to you. -What's up?
我有事要跟你說 怎麼了？
I've been thinking about this commercial thing. Me against Ben.
我一直在想這次拍廣告的事 我和班硬碰硬
The two of us competing. That can't lead to anything good.
捉對廝殺 這樣橫豎都不會有好結果
I think I'm just gonna step aside. I'll tell them that I won't audition.
我想我還是退出好了 告訴他們我不去試鏡
Joey, that's great. Thanks,man.
喬伊，太好了，多謝
That's it?
就這樣？
You're gonna let me do this? It's my career we're talking about!
你真要讓我這樣做？ 這事關我的職業生涯耶
But you just
可是你說…
I just said that so you wouldn't let Ben do it.
我是要套你說出讓班退出
If anyone should step aside, it should be Ben.
羅斯，如果真有人要退出 那也應該是班
-What? -Chandler,tell him!
什麼？ 錢德，告訴他為什麼
Well, let me get the door first.
我先去開門
Hi,no one!
沒有人，你好
Why should Ben step aside?
班為什麼應該退出？
It was his audition in the first place. You tagged along.
這原本就是他的試鏡 你是跟過去的
You're like the tagalong dad!
就像是跟班老爹
At least I care about his feelings.
起碼我有顧慮到班的感受
What?
什麼？
You know how hard it'll be on him when he doesn't get it?
你知道萬一他沒通過試鏡 到時他會有多難過嗎？
And why wouldn't he get it?
那他又為什麼不會通過？
Come on!
得了吧？
Have you seen what my kid can do?
你有沒有看過 跟我同組的小子有多厲害？
He dials phones, he eats tortilla chips.
他會撥電話、吃墨西哥脆片
He plays soccer with the cartoon tiger!
還會憑空踢足球演對手戲呢
Are you saying your kid eats soup better than my kid?
你是說你的小子喝湯 比我兒子厲害？
You just give him a spoon,baby.
你兒子才剛學會喝湯呢
Oh,yeah? I guess we'll see!
是嗎？我們走著瞧
This commercial belongs to me and Mitch!
好啊，這支廣告片的主角 非我和米契莫屬
-Your kid's name is Raymond! -Yeah? So is yours!
你的孩子叫做雷蒙 對，你的也是！
（中央咖啡館）
-How did work go? -lt was great.
有沒有用？ 很棒…
I went down there like you said. And we talked business.
我聽你們的建議 去她們抽煙的地方 我們討論到了生意
And Kim took my opinions.
阿金完全接受我的意見
You stink!
你渾身煙味
-Thanks. -No,I'm serious.
多謝 我是說真的
That's because I went down there and they were smoking.
因為那裡的人全都在抽煙
This is actually the smell of success.
這其實是成功的味道
But there's something different
不過有點怪怪的
Oh,my God! You smoked!
天啊，你有抽煙
I did not.
我沒有
Yes, you did. You look happy and sick. You smoked!
才怪，你看起來生病又快樂 你一定有抽煙
All right, fine! But I had to. I had to do it for my career.
好啦…我有抽 為了事業不得已
I wish I had to smoke for my career.
好羨慕
But it's so gross!
這樣很噁心耶
It's not that bad, you know?
沒那麼糟啦
Yeah,my tongue feels a little fuzzy and my fingers sort of smell.
雖然舌頭有點打結 手指也有點怪味
I actually feel like I could throw up.
其實我感覺快吐了
-Can you hear yourself? -I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
聽你自己在說什麼 我知道…我也很後悔
I'm not myself. I smoked like half a pack.
我都不是我自己了 我抽了半包煙
I feel a little shaky and a little weird.
感覺怪怪的，還在發抖
But you gotta push past this, okay? Because it's about to get so good.
好，但你一定要撐過這一關 再來就會是快樂無比了
錢德
You smell so smoky, I gotta get up.
你渾身煙味，我得去透透氣
I'm not kidding.
我沒騙你
I think you smell great.
我覺得你聞起來很香
So we're decided. No on plaid, yes on pink.
所以大家都同意了 不要格子圖案，要粉紅？
Absolutely.
完全正確
I'm so onboard.
我舉雙手雙腳贊成
-Didn't you just light that? -Yeah.
瑞秋，這支煙不是才剛點？ 是啊
But you know what?
但是...
I'm just really,really trying to cut back, you know.
我正在努力少抽煙
Good luck, Rach.
「瑞秋，我等著看笑話」
I've been thinking about quitting.
其實我最近有想要戒煙
Every Sunday night, I tell myself I'm quitting.
那可不，我每週日晚上 都告訴自己要戒煙
Every Monday morning, it's like:
結果週一還不是狂抽猛抽
Tell me about it.
還用你說
We'll just quit. Let's all quit!
那就戒了吧，我們一起戒煙
It sounds appealing.
聽起來是很誘人啦
-I never could do it. -But you could. Absolutely.
我戒煙從沒成功過 你可以的，一定行
We can help each other. We could get those patches.
我們可以互相幫忙 用那個什麼戒煙貼布的
We could be like the Patch Sisters.
我們能組成戒煙三姐妹
You know,we really should quit. Okay, let's quit!
其實我們真的應該戒煙 好吧，一起來戒煙
Great! Give me those cigs. Come on!
太棒了，把香煙給我 來
Give it! Out. Done. Quit.
通通交出來
My late husband gave me that lighter.
那個打火機是我先夫送我的
I'm not kidding.
我沒在開玩笑
Okay,then.
那好吧
Mmm...soup.
湯
Joey, Ross is gonna be here any second, would you mind watching Ben for me while I use the ladies' room?
喬伊，羅斯隨時會到 我去上個廁所 幫我看一下班，好嗎？
-No problem. -Thanks.
好啊，沒問題 謝謝
嗨，班
So you want to be an actor? I gotta tell you, it's no picnic.
你想當演員啊？ 告訴你，演戲可不像野餐
There's tons of rejection. No stability.
有碰不完的釘子 一點都不穩定
I mean,one day, you're Dr. Drake Ramoray.
前一天你還是德瑞克醫生
The next day,you're eating ketchup out of the bottle.
隔天你就要去啃番茄醬
It's a tough life. I mean, sure, you can get up whenever you want...
這可是艱苦的生活 沒錯啦，你是能決定起床時間
...watch TV all day...
整天看電視也行
...meet tons of women in acting class....
在演員訓練班裡 認識一卡車的女孩
Oh, who am I kidding. I can't talk you out of this. It's a great life.
小子，我幹嘛勸你打消念頭 這種生活太棒了
-Joey. -Ross.
喬伊 羅斯
Ben.
班
I mean,Ben. Ben.
班…
Raymond, Joey, you're up.
雷蒙，喬伊，該你們上場了
So here's what....
好，現在要…
Are you sure that I haven't seen you somewhere before?
我一定有在哪裡見過你
No, I haven't been in any plays.
沒有，我都待在家
All right,let's try one. Whenever you guys are ready.
好吧，我們來試一次 你們準備好了就開始
Is there a problem?
有問題嗎？
Well,this is noodle soup. And I've been working with tomato.
這是麵湯 我練習時是用番茄湯
But that's okay. No problem.
不過沒關係…
Mmm...noodle soup.
麵湯…
You know,that's fine. But the line is,"Mmm...soup."
你那樣不錯 不過台詞是「湯」
-What'd I say? -"Mmm...noodle soup."
那我剛才說什麼？ 「麵湯」
How's that different?
有什麼不一樣？
對…
All right. Let's try one.
好，我們來試一次
Mmm...
...noodle soup.
麵湯
Let's do it again.
好，我們再來一次
Mmm...soup.
湯
I mean, noodle soup. I mean, soup!
我是說「麵湯」 不對，是「湯」
Come on!
你爭氣點
You know what? We need to move on.
我們得換下一組了
No,I could do it one more time.
不…我再演一次
Look.
你看
Mmm...noodle soup.
麵湯…
Damn it!
可惡！
So I think that if we get these samples into the magazine by Monday,we'll be fine.
週一前把樣品交給雜誌社 應該就沒問題了
Sounds good. So, Rach, how you doing?
聽起來不錯  瑞秋，你還好嗎？
-I'm great! -No, with the not-smoking thing.
好極了 不，我是說戒煙的事
Kill me now.
可把我給搞死了
Let me tell you something, I ate 40 Mallomars today.
跟你說 我今天吃了40個棉花糖
I mean, I have patches all over my body, you know?
全身貼滿了戒煙貼布
-I mean,I haven't slept in two days. -We quit yesterday.
我連續兩天都失眠 我們昨天才戒煙的
That's counting today.
我連今天都算進去了
But anyway, so these samples,I think
言歸正傳，我想這些樣品…
Oh,my God!
天啊
I'm so sorry, I forgot. I have to go to the mailroom and mail some proofs.
我忘記了，真的很抱歉 我得去收發室寄送樣張
Go ahead. Rachel and I will just sit here and keep brainstorming.
儘管去 我和瑞秋繼續來腦力激盪
Also,Vogue called. And they were wondering
時尚雜誌也想知道… 你知道嗎？…
You know what? I'm a little hungry. I'm just gonna run down to the vending machines.
我有點餓了 我要去販賣機買東西
All right.
好吧
Busted!
被逮到了
Come on! What are you doing? I thought we were the Patch Sisters.
你們這是在幹嘛？ 我們不是戒煙姐妹花嗎？
That didn't work out.
對，那樣行不通
Wait a minute. What about all we've talked about?
那我們說過的那些事呢？
You know,the disgusting place, the ugly people.
說這噁心的地方，醜陋的人
Hey,how you doing?
你好嗎？
We tried to quit. But it was too hard.
瑞秋，我們有試著戒煙 但那實在是太難了
If you started smoking again, you could have at least told me.
你們開始抽煙 起碼也該告訴我嘛
Give me one of those. What are we talking about?
快點來一支，剛才說到哪裡？
No! You're doing great! Don't you give up.
不行，你戒煙很成功 不許放棄
That's why we didn't tell you, and we won't drag you down.
所以我們才沒跟你說 我們不想拖你下水
Wait. No,no. Drag me down.
等等，別這樣，拖我下水…
Forget it. We're so proud of how well you're doing.
瑞秋，萬萬不可 你戒煙成功，我們都替你驕傲
I won't let you blow it. If I catch you, you're fired.
我不能讓你前功盡棄 若被我捉到 我一定炒你魷魚
Go on,get out of here. I don't want you breathing this stuff.
走吧，離開這裡 我不要你吸二手煙
So, okay. You'll come with me on the Paris trip?
好，你和我一起去法國出差
Oh,man!
要命！
Check it out. Cup hat, cup banner...
你瞧瞧，杯子帽 杯子布條
...cup chandelier, and the thing that started it all: the cup!
杯子吊燈  還有本尊：杯子
Great job with the cups.
菲比，你對杯子還真有一套
Why don't you just go out with her?
你乾脆跟她去約會算了
Did you notice the ice? Look!
你有沒有注意到冰？
We have it all. We have crushed, cubed and dry. Watch.
各式各樣的都有 有碎冰、冰塊 還有乾冰 注意看
Mystical.
很有神秘感吧？
Everyone-no one's eating my Tuscan finger food. Because they're all filling up on Phoebe's snow cones!
沒人想吃我的小點心 他們全跑去吃菲比的雪花冰
There are snow cones?
有雪花冰？
Snow cones! Yuck!
雪花冰最噁心了！
-Go,go! Right there! -Thank you.
你去吃啦 謝謝…
菲比？
-You really did do a nice job. -Thank you...
你做的很棒 謝謝你
...for stating the obvious.
看就知道
I deserve that.
我活該
I just want you to know that if we ever cohost a party together again...
我只是要讓你知道 若我們下回再一起主辦派對
-...you can do whatever you want. -Joey's got a birthday coming up.
你想要怎麼做都行 喬伊的生日快到了
-Really? What do you wanna do? -Okay,I'd like to be in charge of beer.
真的？ 那你要怎麼幫他慶祝？ 好，我想要負責啤酒
Well,then there's nothing left for me.
那我就沒的做了
-Look,look! -Surprise!
注意！… 驚喜！
What? My birthday is not for another month.
什麼啊？ 一個月後才是我生日啊
That's the surprise.
這樣才驚喜啊
Oh,my God, you guys! This is so great! It's so unexpected.
天啊，你們太棒了 我完全沒想到
I mean,Chandler's birthday is even before mine.
錢德的生日還比我早到呢
Surprise!
驚喜！
This is so great! Look at all these...
真是太棒了，看看這些...
...cups.
...杯子
This is so weird.
真是怪怪的
I was in charge of cups.
杯子是我負責的
Oh,okay. Not so weird.
好，那就沒那麼怪了
-Chandler, what are you doing? -Nothing.
錢德，你在幹嘛？ 沒幹嘛
-What's in your hand? -Money. I'm stealing all the money.
你手裡拿是什麼？ 錢，我偷走了所有的錢
Chandler.
錢德
But just one, okay? Because nobody knows when my birthday is.
抽一支就好 因為沒有人記得我的生日
Let me make this clear to you,okay?
或許這能讓你清醒一點
It's either that...
有香煙…
...or this.
就沒有我
They were menthol.
剛才那是薄荷煙
Listen, man. I'm sorry the audition didn't go well.
我很遺憾你試鏡不順利
Yeah, right.
是喔
No, really. I am, Joey. I feel bad.
喬伊，我是真的很遺憾
Look, Ross. You don't have to,okay?
羅斯，你用不著遺憾
It's not your fault I suck.
是我自己遜，怨不得你
What kind of an actor can't even say, "Mmm...noodle soup"?
連「麵湯」都說不好 還算哪門子的演員？
You know what? Maybe you didn't mess up your audition because you suck.
你知道嗎？或許你搞砸了試鏡 不是因為你遜
Maybe you messed up because you care more about your godson.
或許你搞砸了試鏡 是因為你更在意你的教子
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
I think, subconsciously
我認為，在潛意識裡…
You lost me.
等等，我聽不懂
I think,on some level, you sabotaged...
我覺得在某種程度上 你破壞了....
...your own audition so Ben would get the part.
自己的試鏡 才好讓班拿到那個角色
Your way sounds a lot better than mine.
你的說法比我的好多了
It's not that I'm a bad actor.
對，不是我演技爛
No,it's just that I care so damn much about little Ben...
對 只是我考慮的都是班
...that it was more important for me to see him succeed.
看到他成功對我來說更重要
-There you go. Thank you. -Thank you.
就是這樣，謝謝你 謝謝你
-So did he get it? -No.
那他拿到角色沒？ 沒有
What are you gonna do?
不如意事十之八九嘛
Excuse me, is Rachel Green here? I'm meeting her for lunch.
不好意思，瑞秋葛林在嗎？ 我跟她約了吃中飯
She doesn't come down anymore. You can find her up on 10.
她現在不會下來這裡了 她在十樓
Okay,great.
好…
So we talked about the presentation.
我們昨天中飯聊到提案報告
He wondered if one person would be enough.
他擔心一個人出差不夠看
And I said, "Yeah,absolutely."
我說絕對沒問題
I'll catch you guys later.
後會有期了